This is my 14 day product review.  This
product was quite expensive for me.
My expenses till delivery were around ₹5 lakh.  It
is quite expensive and if I talk about the features, it has a
CEO attitude.  Madam
works at USF.  Three managers have been appointed
who are always ready for them.
And if I talk about the sound quality, it is quite
loud.  If you want to
hear the sound after 2:00 pm then madam is definitely present.
And if I talk about its battery, then
its battery has to be charged every 1 hour.
So, this is all that has been revealed so far
in the last 14 days.  Yes, I would like to say one more thing.
Madam does not like light, sound and touch at all.
She
has quite the attitude of an MD CO.  Look how it's
looking at me, what is it doing?